jomres.net 2019-04-09

# Jomres the Online Booking System for Joomla and WordPress - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: 06 April 2018

**Woollyinwales IT** ("us", "we", or "our") operates [http://www.jomres.net](http://www.jomres.net/) (the "Site").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information") and email address. This information is used to administer your account and process orders.

We have not, and will never, share your information with third parties. The only exception to this are payment gateways we use to provide trials/payments for services. Please see their sites for their specific privacy policies.

We do not store ANY information that your Jomres installation generates. Your clients are just that, yours, they're not our and we do not request or store any of their information.

### How long do we store your information for?

Unless you specifically request it, we will store the information you save in your account indefinately, both for tax purposes and to maintain a record of your licenses. If you raise a ticket, again we will store this information indefinately as having a record of our interactions with you allows us to ensure that we are providing you with the best possible service.

You can, at any time, request that we remove your information. Please contact us via the ticket system. So long as you do not have any active licenses with us, we will be happy to anonymise all of your personally identifyable information.

### Download your data

You can download the PII data that we store for you via your account, menu option "Download you data". On that page we you will see two separate information fields. The first field shows your PII as stored in the license server. The second field shows any ticket posts associated with your email address.

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information through newsletters or other communications, however we will never share this information with third parties. We send out newsletters occasionally, but _you must_ opt into receiving those newsletters, and you can unsubscribe at any time. Most updates are provided through our Facebook and Twitter feeds, and through the Jomres Control Panel itself.

[edit April 2018] At this moment in time new users cannot subscribe to newsletters. We prefer to share information through Facebook, Twitter, Github and the forum.

### ​Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site, such as the forum or the shop.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 26 April 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this  
page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://www.jomres.net/contact).
